[{"answer": "I don't know. Experience. Freedom. Love... Now. Peyote's like love. When it's given it's blessed. When it's sold it's damned. I like peyote. I like acid, it's easier to get. I like the spiritual voyage. The first time I did acid I saw God. I did. I had a friend who was Christ. And he was my friend too. I suddenly knew the secret of everything", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I think you're alive by recognizing beauty", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I bet your dad's a school teacher", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "\"...but one, the most beautiful one of all dances in a ring of fire and throws off the challenge with a shru", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I wrote it for you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Whatcha been doing", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Songs? Lemme hear one", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "IDs! IDs! Can't get in without an I.D.", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I forgot my list", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So you don't have a phone number? What do you mean you don't have a phone number", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I don't have a phone", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Hey Ray, why don't you change your name to my friend or my friend or something... it's only a word y'know", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "HA HA HA!! WILL YOU DIE FOR ME", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'D DIE FOR ANYBODY", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Did you know my friend said,", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Part of the clown's wisdom", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "About what", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " What's your problem with fathers! They're dead, both of them, I told you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well you see my friend there's this crazy girl in here, she's just lying on the bed with her legs open and I don't know what to do", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " It's your cousin my friend, you don't want to see her. Go home", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "HOW MUCH", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "You figured? What the fuck is this my friend", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Cause I don't want to participate in anything that would accomplish your goal", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "\"Death old frien", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "They'll still be talking about my friend when you're a walk on my friend. I'll make you a deal. When you do something, I'll criticize it", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You should take it outta your ass", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "That wasn't THE FUCKING IDEA MAN!! We're gonna sue you!... We're pulling the plug", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": " We're not playing", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "my friend, wouldn't it be better to have a kid with someone who wanted to be its father", "docId": "Doors_-The.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It'd be a monster", "qsentId": 32}]